Metal Cardbot Commentary!
The Mischievous Shadow X!
Hey, everyone! Jun here!
Let's watch another episode of Metal Cardbot together!
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Shadow X, setup!
Hey, everybody! My name is Shadow X!
I wanted to be in one of these things, too!
Nice to meet you, Shadow X!
Today, let's watch the story
of when the prankster Shadow X showed up!
Shall we get started?
Pass it here!
Jun! What game were you playing here?
Oh, this is Soccer!
You win by getting the ball in the other team's goal.
Wouldn't it be easier to just pick it up with your hands and put it in?
Then that would make it basketball...
Then what about hitting it with a stick and sending it flying?
That's baseball!
Wait a minute... you already know this, don't you?
Jun is the most fun to tease!
What just happened?
Okay, bye!
Anna! See you tomorrow!
Jun?
You should watch where you're going.
What was that?
It does seem like a childish prank.
Who are you calling childish?!
Who's there?!
What was that?!
Is it invisible?
What? What's going on?
Haha!
Show yourself!
You must be a Metal Cardbot like us!
So you figured out, huh?
Stealth mode, off!
A plane that can hide turn invisible...
Shadow X, you're pretty cool!
Aren't I?
But I'm not a plane, I'm a helicopter!
Oh, right!
Theo explained it best.
He said you're some kind of jet, right?
HE! LI! COP! TER!
Technically speaking, a VTOL! Vertical Take-Off and Landing aircraft!
V..T?... That's too hard to remember!
Can't I just call you an airplane?
Tch... Jun, are you just doing this on purpose?!
Heheh! It's revenge for earlier!
So that was all you!
Why are you pulling pranks on everyone?
Isn't it obvious?
I. Just.
Don't.
Like.
You!
Jun! Why is she taking a video of herself dancing?
Is she giving it as a gift or something?
No~
Vera wants to be famous on the internet.
Huh?!
I wanna be famous too! I wanna dance!
You can't!
The identity of the Metal Cardbots needs to remain a secret!
We aren't allowed to be here! Let's get out of here before we get in trouble!
Hang on. Something doesn't seem right.
Hey! Vera!
He's going up towards the cranes!
First, we'll need to get Shadow X to come down!
Ha! Took you long enough to get here!
You're so slow! I was getting bored!
This guy...
Blue Cop! Prepare for battle!
Alright.
Blue Cop!
Haha! Looks like I won, blue-haired kid!
Too bad! Looks like I won't become one of your underlings.
You keep saying underling...
but I have never made any Metal Cardbot my underling!
You're so obsessed with underlings. What would you do if you had an underling of your own?
If I had an underling, I'd boss them around like crazy!
You can't do that!
Bossing others around isn't nice!
I'd play hide-and-seek with my underling in stealth mode!
Just try and find me! Hard, right? Heheh!
Does Shadow X treat his friends like underlings...?
But only if you can defeat us!
What?
Let's have a rematch, Shadow X!
I promise I will seal you for sure!
Next time we meet, I'll be sure to blow you away with my Heli-Tornado!
That's what you think. But I have a secret weapon that can beat your Heli-Tornado!
Huh? A secret weapon?!
I-I accept your challenge!
Next time we meet, we will see if your secret weapon can beat my Heli-Tornado!
I'm not leaving because I'm scared of some "secret weapon" or anything.
Don't take this the wrong way!
Well, everyone?
This is the first time I failed to seal a Cardbot...
In any case, look forward to the next "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!